You like toys.
おもちゃ好きなんだね
Too strong?
強すぎ?
No more
もうダ
Mail?
メ?
You haven't gone yet, have you?
まだ 行ってないよね?
went?
行 った?
Did you go?
行ったの?
You have to tell me.
教えなきゃダメだよ
It's no good anymore.
もうダメだよ
Try touching it.
触ってみて
強
stomach?
い?
Something even more powerful.
も っと強力なものを
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Okay.
いいよ
Inhale.
吸い込む
No.
ダメ
Let's do a little bit.
ちょっとやろう
Inhale, inhale.
吸い込んで、吸い込んで
Even though it makes me laugh.
笑うのに
It seems so.
そうやらしいね
I'm also smoking octopus.
たこも吸ってるよ
Let me know when you go.
行くときにくっと教えて
I can't do it anymore.
もう無理
what up?
どうした?
Are you sweating?
汗だくなっちゃった?
hot?
熱い?
Shall we take a break?
休憩する?
Okay.
いいよ
Please sleep.
寝ててね
Shall we take a break?
休憩する?
Are you going to take a break?
休憩するの?
Don't you like it?
嫌だ?
Aren't you sweating?
汗かいてない?
I was sweating profusely.
湧き汗もすごい
Don't you like it?
嫌だ?
You've never done it, right?
やったことないでしょ?
A new one.
新しいやつ
It might feel good.
気 持ちいいかも
This feels good, right?
これ気持ちいいでしょ?
it hurts?
痛い?
Looks disgusting.
気持ち悪そう
tell me.
教えて
It's impossible.
無理じゃん
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
I'll definitely go again.
ちゃんとまた行くんだよ
Continue.
続けて
It's not scary.
怖くない
I don't like it.
嫌だ
The sound is amazing.
音すごいね
I went again.
また行った
Let's go one last time.
最後もう一回行こう
最後
What's the difference?
何が違う?
tell me.
教 えて
What's the difference?
何が違う?
First, the size of the hunt.
まず、狩りの大きさ
Which is the bigger hunt?
狩りの大きさ、どっちが大きい?
The hunt was small.
狩りが小さかったな
Be honest.
正直言いなさい
About the same.
同じくらい
What's the shape?
形は?
What shape?
どういう形?
what happened?
どうしたの?
Not at all.
全然違う
How is it different?
どういうふうに違う?
Is it warped?
反ってんの?
this.
これ
I don't understand.
分 かんない
If it's warped, it's the upper wall, when I did it with normal intentions.
反ってると上の方の壁、正常意でやった時ね
Because it will collapse.
崩れるからさ
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいかな
Feel like shaking?
揺れたくなった?
hey.
ね
Because I can't do mambo.
俺マンボダメだから
I'll do it on this side.
俺 こっち側にやるから
Together as we get used to each other.
なれながら一緒に
Go for two.
2個も行け
Have you ever done that?
したことある?
this.
これ
Have you ever been Gareth?
ガレスしたことある?
Me and him.
僕、彼と
be?
ある?
be.
ある
Does it hurt?
痛いの?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
It's okay to say it.
言っちゃっていいんだろ
What did you come from?
何から来たの?
Tice.
タイス
Would you like to ride it?
乗ってみる?
This side.
こっち側
this?
この?
Yes, this tree.
うん、この木で
You've never done it before, it's so easy.
やったことないでしょ、こんなに簡単に
it hurts?
痛い?
it hurts.
痛い
tell me.
教えて
it hurts.
痛い
It hurts.
痛いって
Did you say something funny?
キチャキチャ言ったの?
Yeah.
うん
I have to go ahead and do it.
チンチンと行かないとね
I don't know.
わからない
it hurts.
痛い
what up?
どうした?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
what up?
どうした?
Did you pull it out?
抜いちゃったの?
what up?
どうした?
When you go, you have to take the line.
行くときは線で行かないと
Did you pull it out?
抜いちゃったの?
Impossible.
無理
I guess it feels good because it's raw?
生だから気持ちいいのなんでしょう?
Have you never said that?
言ったことない?
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
yes.
はい
Is it okay to hold on?
も っとついて大丈夫?
or
や
Was it too much?
り すぎた?
That nasty face.
そのやろい顔
Have you gone too many times?
何回も行き過ぎ?
Well then, I'll show you what's naughty.
じゃあ私、やらしいの見せようか
What's going on?
どうなってる?
tell me.
教えて
What's going on?
どうなってる?
What's in it?
何が入ってんの?
Where are you in?
どこに入ってんの?
You couldn't say it now.
今言えなかったのね
It's gotten naughty.
やらしくなったね
I could say it.
言 えちゃったんだ
You couldn't say it at first, right?
最初言えなかったでしょ?
I can say this because it feels good.
気持ちいいから言えるんだ
Give yourself this much too.
自分もこんなに出してね
I said it even though I didn't do anything.
何もしてないのに言っちゃったんだ
Yo.
よ
Raw, it feels good, right?
生、 気持ちいいでしょ?
That's amazing!
すごい言ったじゃんだって
Raw, right?
生、いいでしょ?
Wasn't it good?
良かったでしょ?
It doesn't have to be raw, right?
生じゃなくてもいいでしょ?
It's my first time.
初めてだからね
Let's try it out as many times as we like.
何 回でも出してみようか
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
You can't do it, can you?
できないでしょ?
I'll put it out.
出すよ
Let's get it out.
出そう
Can you lick it?
舐めれる?
Let me know if it's not possible.
無理だったら言って
out
出
I came.
て きた
Move it.
動かして
Ma
マ
Open it.
ン ゴー開いて
ERROR
マンゴー開いて
Man
マ ン
Go open.
ゴ ー開いて
Open it.
開 いて
Are you putting it in?
入れてる?
Please tell me because I can't see it.
見えないから教えて
Cheating?
ズルい?
You can come visit us again.
また寄りに来られる
You won't refund the tuition fee, right?
昇学金返さないでしょ?
It's not enough, right?
足りないでしょ?
It feels good.
気持ちいいもんね
It feels so good.
気持ちよくてこんなに
I got my tuition refund back.
昇学金返されてきた
That's good.
良いじゃん
The child is good.
お子が良いんだ